It's a question of ambition.
Rephrase.
It's a matter of limitation.
And the importance of knowing yours.
Your boss, Tama.
He had a reputation, yes.
But, he also knew where he stood.
Understood how high he should climb.
That's why Bangun let
him be the man he was.
Don't mind them.
I like to think I'm a reasonable man.
Like you, some would consider me ambitious.
But you see, in this world of ours...
it's a "one step at a time”…
kind of thing.
And by my reckoning, you really should have been
some fucking steps away from a meeting… like this.
- Bangun will...
- Bangun is an ol…!
He's on his way out.
I gave you a chance.
You chose him.
So...
I guess this brings us back
full circle, ambition...
and limitation.
Bejo! Bejo!
- Please don't do this.
- I already told you.
- Don't mind him.
- No, Bejo, no!
Bejo, wait!
You called?
Rama.
I know who you are.
My brother says...
you're someone I can trust.
Yeah, he’s right.
They got you bad.
They did.
Take him.
Get him treated.
Be careful.
No, wait! Stop! Stop!
What the fuck?! No! No! No! No!
- What was that?!
- It's okay, it is. Calm down, take a seat.
Sit.
Take his jacket, his gloves and
any official threads he has.
Dump him out deep.
If we’re lucky he’ll float to shore by dawn.
Yes, sir.
Trust me.
He would've never
survived til the morning.
This is the only way we can be sure
he won't say a word about you.
About us.
Us?
You see I run a unit that weeds out
crooked cops like him.
And I could do with someone like
you to help me dig out some more.
We're a small division.
But we're small for a reason. Trust.
I have evidence.
We could've made a case.
I could've testified.
No, all that you have are
hearsay and a box of tapes.
I've been down that road before.
All it does is just cough up
a few more names to take the heat.
No, no, if we're going to
clean up this city...
we have to aim higher. All of them.
Like it or not, you threw a wrench in their
gears today, and they will come for you.
They'll do anything to remove
you from the equation.
If we don't act fast…
you'll be gone… in a week
Your family too.
But it doesn't have to be that way.
Let's say we keep this internal.
If you keep your mouth shut, I’ll make sure
everything gets covered up, nice and clean.
I can protect you.
For you, today never happened.
You were never there.
In their eyes you're still
a rookie for fuck's sake.
They won't even blink an eye at
one name missing from the report.
Is this all of them?
All eighteen.
No survivors.
What do you think?
Reza.
I'll keep looking.
I'll take care of it personally.
No exceptions.
What do you want?
I want you on my team,
to go under-cover.
You'll be re-trained. Given the skills
to do what we need, when we need it.
It’s for the good of this city.
What do you say?
No. Not interested.
Come again?
Sir...with all due respect.
I brought him in to do time.
To take account of his life!
And we put a bullet in him
to protect yours!
There's no such thing as a clean war
in this world. Open your eyes!
Believe me, my eyes are wide open, sir!
We may be after the same thing...
but I'm not going to follow the
same path as you to get there.
Who killed him?
My brother.
His name is Bejo.
He's been on the up for some time now.
I know the name.
Rama...
your brother had big enemies.
But trust me, they're absolutely nothing
compared to what's coming for you.
I can provide safety
for your wife and child.
We can keep them out of reach.
But I need you.
Right now...
this city is carved up...
between our local kingpin, Bangun...
and the Goto family from Japan.
Tama, he answered to Bangun.
And that building was the perfect way to pay
whoever he needed to without us knowing.
If we get you close
enough to Bangun...
then we can weed out the rest
of those crooked bastards.
Rama...
for this to end,
I need those names.
I need evidence that puts Reza’s
hands in Bangun’s pockets.
What's the next step?
Uco, his only child…
He's serving time in prison.
It's the perfect opportunity.
Get in, get close.
Meaning?
I have to arrest you.
It will be a few months.
You can't know where I am.
I can't be seen
anywhere near you… or Angga.
But, if I don't do this,
I can't protect us this time.
Please understand.
This is the only choice.
He's out of the hospital now, right?
I heard he was discharged.
Shut your mouth!
You nod here!
Yes or no! Got it?
So, what did he do?
What did he do?
Enough.
I need more than that.
He's the asshole son of
an asshole politician.
Can't you just put me in, lock me up?
Why does this kid have to bleed?
His daddy is the reason
Uco’s in prison.
If we're talking
earning credibility...
doing this puts you
on his radar.
At the very least,
it gives you two something to talk about.
If I’m going to do this…
Really do this…
I need a better reason.
Alright, how about this.
He is also a major benefactor...
for Bejo.
Rama, listen...
do enough to get inside...
but not enough to keep
you there for good, huh?
Where is he?
Benny and his boys
introduced themselves yesterday…
Which one is Benny?
Him.
Benny and his associates are with me.
Yeah, and you are?
You'll figure that out at some point.
And when you do, maybe you'll show
me a little more fucking respect.
But for now, I'll be tolerant.
So, what do you want?
An apology?
This…
is my ‘just in case’.
There are never enough walls
to cover your back.
Even you.
Especially after your
little ‘display’.
I'm someone who can put walls up.
I can cover your back
anywhere in this place.
You may not know who I am right now.
But when you do,
you'll realize how real my offer is.
Join with us, and own
this wing with me.
We could do with someone
like you on our side.
-  I'm flattered but...
- Don’t make me tap the table again!
With all due respect.
I don't like spending my
time acting tough in toilets.
- Excuse me.
- Listen to me.
In here it’d be wise to pick a side.
Loners don't tend to
last too long in here.
Clearly.
The warden tells me you've
got quite a group here.
I got who I could.
I'm working to get our guys
inside to cover your back.
But until I do,
keep a low profile.
You can't trust any
of these fuckers.
Low profile?
I'm my father's son.
That fact alone
makes me a target here.
All I can do in here
is use it against them.
You just focus on
keeping the knives away.
It would make my job a lot easier
if you'd cool things down here.
When was the last time
you spent inside, Eka?
Keeping quiet isn’t an option.
Unless I want to wake up every
morning with a broom in my ass.
Here’s a start,
find out about that guy.
Why's he here?
Him?
He wheel-chaired your favorite
politician's kid.
Not bad.
His name's Yuda, from the sticks.
He's a ‘nobody’.
Well, that ‘nobody’ took
out 15 of my guys.
Well all right, so he can fight...
So what?
He's clean,
no connections on the outside at all.
Who are you?
I'm the guy gifting you
five years…
just so you can say you belong.
Since you’ve walked in…
they've been eyeballing you,
all trying to get a feel for who you are.
But by sitting here…
I just made you.
But, don’t worry
You can thank me later on.
Oh, yeah, who do I thank for
the fucking three years I got given?
Bunawar said I'd be out in months,
not years.
Did you really think that crook politician
would stop you from being here?
That it would make things ‘even’.
Fair? No.
You went after his son.
211.5
Be glad he showed enough heart
not to come for yours.
I need you to talk to Bunawar.
Nah, I'm just here to show my face.
And I did that already.
Now, you're on your own.
Suck it up, and don't fuck it up.
I rely on you now the same
way you relied on me.
Those bruises will heal.
How does it feel?
Different.
- Gimme that.
- No need.
Fuck you. If I'd parked further away then,
yeah, you can carry it yourself.
But this, this I got.
- It's good to have you out.
- I appreciate what you did for me.
I can use all the help I can get.
Pass on my thanks to your father.
You can do that yourself.
We're going to his office.
So he can thank you.
- He doesn't have to.
- Yes he does.
Okay?
Do you know of a man
goes by the name of Bejo?
Yeah, sounds familiar.
He made a name for himself
when he took out Yudi's group.
He's been making waves of late.
Owns a few restaurants…
and takes care of… problems
for high-profile clients.
The kind that can't afford
to carry a spotlight.
I know him. He came to me… way back,
wanting collateral to set up shop.
I hear that he's looking
to expand his operations.
Where?
That's where the rumors stop.
But you can be sure
it will be one of ours.
… that's right.
I'm sorry, but he can’t
be disturbed now.
Thank you.
- How long will my father be?
- He'll be done soon.
Excuse the mess.
It could be nothing.
I just thought you'd want to know now.
While one of us can still take
care of a situation like him.
I'll have my men
monitor the situation.
If he steps out of line,
we'll take care of it.
Don’t worry.
253.5
Who says I'm worried, asshole?
With respect.
254.5
The respect is mutual.
Mr. Goto.
Ah, there they are!
Ah, glad to finally meet.
- Likewise, sir.
- Yeah.
Your son speaks very highly of you.
Ah, and, so he should.
I want you to know we tried
to get you out much sooner. Yeah?
But you hurt the wrong person.
His father made it damn difficult
to get you a pardon.
It's okay.
Besides, what's done is done.
You're out now.
And now we can move on.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Now take your clothes off.
Sorry?
You heard me.
It's okay, Yuda, just do what he says.
Uco, come on, wait a second…
Listen.
It's not that I don't trust you.
I just don't trust anybody.
If the worse that happens is that you suffer
the indignity of an old man seeing your
cock then I'd say you got off light.
Take them off.
Everything.
Arms up.
Turn around.
Check them.
All clear.
Turn around.
Burn them anyway.
Go. Give him something new.
Incinerator.
Now, it's like this...
I will always appreciate
what you did for my boy.
I will never forget that.
But it's not a free pass with me.
I've thanked you in person.
That will make sure you're
looked after while you're here.
But when it comes to the work,
you're no more special than anyone else.
If you fuck up, you're out.
I won't let you down, sir.
So this is your place.
You have pretty much
everything you need.
Anything you don’t…
just call and I’ll
take care of it.
Thanks.
Bangun gave me everything I have.
And he will do the
exact same for you.
Actually, we come from the same place,
you and I.
I hope that's not where
our similarities end.
I'll pick you up tomorrow at 8:00.
Be ready at 7:00.
It's me.
What happened? We lost you.
You're gonna get me fucking killed.
Day one with a wire? Are you kidding me?
You're fresh out of prison,
they wouldn't...
Yeah, well, they fucking checked me anyway.
They burnt all my clothes.
Do they know?
If I hadn't torn that shit out first,
I'd have been burnt with it.
Don't play games with me,
no more surprises.
Not from you. Not again.
Where are you?
No, no, I'm not disclosing that,
and don't you dare trace this fucking call.
I don't want any of you within
a mile of this place.
Calm down, you're safe.
Now, now just listen…
I'm fucking serious,
you could have gotten me killed.
This guy, any hint at all,
and he will sniff it out.
From now on, you follow my lead.
I'll leave a pair of shoes at our RV point.
Fix them up and I'll pick
them up when I'm ready.
You'll know I got them
once they start walking.
- Hold on, I need time to...
- Just get it done.
Angga, stop doing that.
I told you before!
Hello? Hello!?
Isa...
Rama? Where are you?
Are you okay?
I'm safe.
Don't worry about me.
Isa...
everything just went...
I'm so sorry.
Are you both safe?
We're getting by.
Is that Angga?
Yes.
Please let me listen to him.
Don't put him on,
I just want to listen to him.
Please.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Ears to the ground. Eyes everywhere.
With people like these,
you can't predict how they will react.
We could go in smiling or storm in shooting.
And the reaction would still be the same.
These people are reckless,
they don't have their shit together.
If they did, we wouldn't be side-stepping
puddles of piss to get to them.
Focus. Don't let your mind drift.
Not for a second.
Topan.
Uco.
Sorry. Can I help you
with anything?
It's all there in the envelope.
This isn't enough.
Not enough?
But I counted it myself. It's exact.
Oh, yeah.
Go back a month and you're right.
Just like always.
But this month, you're short.
I’d say about $5000.
Take a seat.
Motherfucker, stop shaking around.
Fuck this shit.
Where the fuck did you find this guy?
Hitchhiker.
Hitchhiker. Fuck. Come on!
How do you expect me to work like this.
Seriously, sort it the fuck out.
Let's shoot this thing,
you fucking loser!
Get on with it! Camera, rolling, shooting.
Just fuck that guy's asshole, you stupid bitch!
Sor… Sorry.
I don't understand.
You're kidding, right?
Sit down.
So...
For 20 years,
my father has ensured
that not one cop has never come around
and knocked on your door.
Now you've been free to
operate on our turf,
and we've worked together
peacefully throughout.
But these payments, these envelopes here.
They only cover you for cock and cum.
They don't allow for any...
expansion.
I'm hearing rumblings, Topan.
People are talking.
Seems you and your boys
here are responsible for
some powder circulating
in my father's territory.
No, that? That's just… umm…
You don't have to explain anything.
We already know everything.
Now, with this new enterprise
of yours
you sure as hell don't want some pig's
knuckles rapping at your door.
So, the price just went up.
All you have to do is just
dig a little bit deeper.
Then we can forgive you
this minor indiscretion.
Now if you’d be so kind,
this envelope here, it’s…
still a little bit light.
He did really good.
Hounded him down quickly and cleanly.
You'd swear he’d been
doing it all his life.
Didn't put a foot wrong.
Okay.
Uco, give this to the kid.
You handled it well today.
It will send out the right message
to everyone.
Keep it up.
- Thank you, sir.
- Okay.
- Sir?
- Yes?
I was wondering… erm… what… with
the way things have been.
Maybe it's time for me to start taking
on more responsibility.
Maybe handle some more of our...
Wo.
When the time comes, I'll know.
But it's not now.
Not yet.
Yeah?
Anything else?
No.
Okay, thank you, Uco.
Thank you.
Would you like a drink?
No, I'm fine, thanks.
Come on, man, drink a little.
Pour the man a drink.
I'm fine, I've had enough.
If you won't drink, then sing at least.
You've been so damn quiet since you got here.
I’m good. I'll just watch.
Fuck, you don't drink, you won't sing.
You should have told me earlier.
We could be at a titty bar hooking up with
Uzbeki girls instead of sweating in here.
Being ignored by these cheap skanks.
Hey, who the fuck are
you calling skanks?
I'm so much more than you,
and you should know that already.
- Prick!
- Joanna, don't!
It's okay.
Joanna...
I'm the kind of guy your friend
is rightly afraid of.
Just ask her.
Oh, yeah?! And why is that?!
It's like this.
The place you work,
the place where you live.
The place where you fuck your clients.
My father… well, he owns it all.
And it's my job to make sure that
everyone who works in this city...
remembers to show
their appreciation.
So you're a debt collector?
- I'll sing, pass me the book.
- No!
We’re just talking. She's a big girl...
she can say what she wants.
Exactly!
Go ahead, keep drinking.
It'll numb the pain for later.
What did you just say?
I said...
it's your turn to sing.
I don't want to sing,
I want to know what you just said.
You either sing or you fuck!
You fucking whore!
Or try both! You wanna sing?!
Last chance! You wanna fuck or sing.
Which is it? Make a decision!
You wanna sing?
Okay, let's pick a song.
Wait! I’ll get the song book!
Where's the fucking songbook?!
Quick, we're waiting to sing.
Hey! Don't fucking touch that!
Don't dare!
This is the problem with
this damn country.
Everyone promises everything.
Everything is yes, yes, yes!
But when it comes time to collect,
it all changes.
"Oh, I'm sorry, I can't."
Bullshit!
But, no, not tonight!
Now, sing.
Is everything… okay here, sir?
We're all good.
Everything's fine.
So, is everything fine?
- You see. We're all happy here.
- Please let me go!
- Close the door on your way out.
- Please help us!
Take the girls with you.
Uco.
Get out!
Sir… it’s on us tonight.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I don't care
what some hooker says.
It's that she had the fucking nerve
to think she was allowed to say it.
I'm much more than that.
More than all this.
It's my fucking time, Yuda.
Why can’t he see that too.
- He will. I’m sure.
- Oh, yeah? When?
Wait here.
Hello?
You know, I’ve seen many a man
pass by me in my time.
Men who could have lasted a little
longer had they known when to stop.
But they don't.
No surprise.
They all end up in the same place.
That same shallow ditch.
A fading memory.
Fill it with rocks this time.
That's the reality.
If you follow us,
follow us.
Simple.
They burn out real fast.
I see it in him, Uco.
I try to ignore it.
But, I know Uco has that fire.
I had to lose a lot in my life before I
could truly see what was important to me.
I don't want the same
to happen to my boy.
He won't, sir.
The time I've known him,
he speaks only highly of you.
I hope you're right.
But I know what my gut tells me.
It seems that you’re his shadow these days.
So if anything comes up…
Anything at all,
you come and tell me right away.
Otherwise, it's like I said...
Bit further down the line the same place
and the same shallow ditch.
I hope for your sake you can swim.
Toss them back in.
Nothing tastes good here.
Our main difference
can be defined by one word.
Legacy.
Every step that I take is a step
forward for my family.
Every step that you take...
is cloaked in the
shadow of your father.
I can exist in this world
With no set of rules to follow.
No expectations of
who I should become.
No rules to abide by.
My father...
he was a fucking road sweeper.
Shining shoes would have made me
a success story compared to him.
You and I…
we couldn't be more different.
But deep inside,
our ambitions are the same.
After all, you came here
of your own accord.
Now we've eaten well,
drank good wine...
and I’d like to think that you would
know even now.
that should I be in the business
of making demands
all I’d need to do is
point a fucking gun at your head.
But that's not how… I do business.
Not today at least.
Today I'm offering you a gift.
An opportunity.
Something, I’m sad to say,
your father chose to keep from you.
Please.
Those prison gates opened
and not one person
from your group was
there to pick them up.
Imagine…
my surprise.
Imagine their surprise when
my men picked them up...
and brought them here...
for… you.
That's my gift.
I give you the opportunity...
now claim your revenge.
And after that?
We will talk business.
Y’know, if it’s financial help you need.
It’s muscle.
Oh, that I can do.
What do you want exactly?
I've got my eye on this patch of land.
Whose land?
That's why I need you.
There’s only two possibilities.
I'm sorry.
But with all due respect.
If I wanted to rent a patch of land...
fair and square,
I'd be meeting your father.
Not you.
It belongs to the Japanese.
It’s the perfect spot for expansion.
Then why are you meeting with me?
It's their land.
My father would never allow it.
He would never do anything
to disrupt the truce.
Again, I’m not interested in
what your father thinks.
I need your support for this,
and if I can be frank...
it seems you need
my support also.
Come again?
Talk around town suggests the top brass
aren't happy anymore with your daddy.
Times are changing.
The Goto family are starting
to make connections.
Top connections.
When your father leaves the office,
he goes home, he sleeps.
Meanwhile, Goto's boy is taking Reza and his men
to titty bars and drowning them in whiskey.
You’d be surprised of how easy it is to sway a cop
or a politician with a little cash and a lot of pussy.
What can I do for you?
Give me your word,
and I'll put an end to the truce.
Put your faith in me and I'll tip the odds
in your favor when the war begins.
You’ll have everything.
And people will see how you took charge
and made your family bigger than it's ever been.
And you? What's your angle?
I’m in this for the long run.
We carve up Goto's land, run this city side by side,
and I get a small patch to myself.
Free of charge.
No questions asked.
And how do you propose
to start a war between us?
Not a drop of blood has been
spilled in 10 years.
That would have to change.
Good boy.
If you expect him to put
his men to war with the Gotos...
it'll take a lot more than
just the death of a foot soldier.
I already have someone in mind for that.
Yeah. Alright, I’ve gotta go.
597.5
Okay. So, same time next month.
Dwi. Wait.
What is it?
- What about Karim?
- What about him?
Dwi... you promised.
No, I said when the time is right.
And it’s not now.
His friends come here, Koso.
Do you think he wants to explain
to them that this is his father?
You don't have to do that, I get it.
- But, please, I haven't seen him since he was...
- Yeah, and whose choice was that?
It was yours. You're the one
who chose to do what you do.
It’s to support you.
There are millions of fathers in the
world supporting their families.
Only they don't come home
with blood on their hands.
Do you realize that what you
do is disgusting?
- I'm not a smart man.
- No, you're not!
But you used to
be a good one.
Regardless, I have the
right to see my son.
That's the thing, no you don't.
Not like this.
And I don't want to hear
anymore about change.
It's been 15 years already,
and I barely recognize you anymore.
Sorry, I have to go.
As always.
Crazy.
Seems anyone can get
in here these days.
Way back this place had class.
But now you see white guys
walking around in sandals...
drinking beer cheaper than the skanks they fuck
in the toilets, like fucking animals.
It's a fucking disgrace.
It needs to go back like it used to…
when it was ours.
When it was more.
Back then, if my father turned up,
the room would freeze.
They’d fear him.
Because they knew,
he could do anything.
Well, times change.
They may not fear him
like they used fear him.
But your father hasn't lost
that fire in his stomach.
He just learned how to control it.
They respect him now.
He doesn't need fear no more.
He has their respect…
and that's what counts.
Yeah used to count.
Used to. No, not anymore.
Times change faster than you think.
Now we got all these people now who don't
give a shit about back then.
They only care about now.
Respect?
That doesn't mean shit to them.
That ain't nothing new. We faced punks
more times than I care to remember.
Trust me...
they don't ever last.
And when it's your turn to take up
the reins you'll see for yourself.
They'll burn and fall in front of you
just like they did for your father.
That same fire is in you, Uco.
I've seen it ever since
you were a child.
Don't ever lose it,
and if you learn to control it…
nothing can stop you from becoming
a great man like your father.
Koso...
you've always been
a good friend to us.
Your father has always
taken good care of me.
To family.
I'll be right back, gotta piss.
The Chinks say they saw the Japs
attacking Koso in that alleyway.
Can you believe that shit?
After all this time, how can they fuck us like this?
We have to respond!
Busting some heads and going to war
are two very different things.
Prakoso's line of work
made him enemies.
Not just the Gotos.
Hell, even the Chinese wanted his head.
This wasn't the first time
he'd been under attack.
Sadly it was the last.
- Where the fuck have you been?
- What happened?
After everything he did for us,
this is how we repay him?
All Koso ever cared for in
the world was his wife...
and kid.
He had no time at all, especially
making things personal.
So, from now on, we’ll
take care of his family.
But we will not retaliate.
672.5
What?
Fuck!
Eka, talk some sense into him.
We're losing our hold here.
Sir... we have ruled this
territory for over 30 years!
And my decision on this
will see us through 30 more!
Stand down! Cool off! Relax.
It’s wise for you… to remember your place.
Uco!
Yuda.
watch over him, take him out...
Get some girl to fuck his mind off this.
Don’t let him do anything stupid.
Yes, boss.
Unbelievable.
Eka...
this is no good.
No good at all.
Uco!
- Come on!
- Who the fuck do you think you are?
Your father's right.
If you rush into this it won't help,
it will make things worse.
Well, you've grown all of a sudden.
I know how you feel…
but you have to let it go.
I've lost control…
- And look where it got me.
- Look where it got you?
It got you a fucking penthouse
suite that I pay for.
I'm just trying to help,
I know how much your...
Fuck you!
Who the fuck do you think you are, huh?
You think you know my father?
You mean nothing to him.
You’re just another thing that we own.
Nothing more.
Pretty soon we’ll be even
and then he’ll cut you free.
What? Did you expect more?
Fuck you!
- Did we get the okay?
- Fuck the okay.
Do it.
It’s on.
"Time for work."
"How many?"
"A few."
Please, have mercy.
Give me the ball.
That was a mistake.
No, wait, please, please, don't!
No!
- Where to?
- Tanah Abang.
Enough.
We settle…
this right now.
Mr. Goto.
Mr. Bangun.
We acknowledge...
this is…
the first show of aggression
between either of you…
in over 10 long years.
There are always casualties.
If this continues...
we will have to put an end to this.
We only acted in retaliation.
Retaliation?
Then how the fuck can you
explain what happened to Prakoso?
That was never an order of ours
Those men had no ties to my father’s grave.
Oh, yeah? Who was it?
Maybe you know?
Sir… with all due respect, but the man you are talking about
was like a brother to my father and an uncle to me.
A man of loyalty to our family for over thirty years.
If you speak ill of him again I swear to god…
Enough!
Only a fool argues…
for the pride of a dead man.
Mr. Goto...
my apologies.
It's fine.
I accept responsibility for this.
What?
Well, it seems that decisions have been made by…
less experienced members
of my organization…
For that I apologize.
And for what’s happened this week.
I will will do what’s needed
to prevent further bloodshed between us.
I thank you sir…
for your swift resolution.
Yes. if you gentlemen would excuse me.
I must tend to my organization.
Of course.
Excuse me.
I heard what happened,
are you okay?
What the fuck!
Why have I got cops attacking me?
Who the fuck made that call?
Calm down.
So far everything seems to suggest
this was purely territorial.
Seems Reza has his men
supporting the Goto family.
- Pull me out now!
- I'm afraid I can't do that.
What do you mean can't?
What have I not witnessed?
Murder, extortion, bribery?
Corruption.
You were never investigating Bangun,
you knew that.
We want the cops they pay.
You think you're alone in this?
This isn't your show, Rama.
None of us are spiders.
We're all just a small part of a big fucking web.
Listen, hold tight.
Your identity is safe.
Where the fuck have you been?
I’ve been trying to reach you.
Get your ass over to the office now
and get Uco the fuck out of here.
Do you realize how many men we lost
just to play your fucking game?!
Everything I've built was for you!
Everything was for you!
And you…
almost brought it to the ground!
You put everything at risk!
And for what?!
For what?
Tell me why?!
Tell me! For what?!
Please, Dad. Listen to me…
please, Dad.
Dad, Dad.
- Please.
- Fuck!
You say you're ashamed of me,
well, I'm ashamed of you Dad!
What the fuck was that?!
Where's your self-respect?!
Apologizing to those stupid motherfuckers!
And in their language...on our land!
And you want to know
what drove me to this?!
I'm tired. I’m tired of waiting!
I can’t just sit back
and do nothing like you!
You had your moment to rage, but where's mine?
What the fuck do I get?
Shaking down junkies for bit change?
That's not the role of a future boss.
That's not work you give a boss!
You've destroyed us.
You've destroyed everything.
Dad.
Dad, everything, everything,
everything that we've lost.
We can… we can get it back.
We can get it all back.
Dad, Dad, trust in me, I can fix this!
I can fix this!
I can fix this…
Enough.
That’t enough.
Eka, prepare a package for the Goto’s.
We'll give them our land
in Menteng and Sabang.
- Yeah?
- Yes, boss.
You can't go in there. He's in...
Forgive me.
You fucking traitor.
How could you do this, Uco?
Eka, run!
What do you want to do with him?
Get rid of him.
What's that?
Yeah, I understand.
Yeah, i’ll call you back.
Reza was just seen
entering Bejo's restaurant.
I thought we'd secured his services.
That was my understanding…
Then why is he meeting Bejo?
Huh?!
Well?!
Bejo, is a fucking nobody,
take care of him now!
- As for the rest of them and Reza…
- Boss, wait.
Bejo is… You see, he’s not alone.
He has Uco with him.
Seems they joined forces...
after taking out Bangun.
Point blank to the head.
Bejo...
has serious numbers now.
He's a threat.
Huh, it seems everything is possible.
What should we do?
We go to war!
If he pulled a trigger
on his own father...
he won't hesitate to come for us.
We start over.
I want them in the ground.
Reza and the rest of those crooks too.
Wait a minute, you can't be serious!
They're not cops anymore.
They're in my world now.
Eka! Eka!
I know who you are.
I know what you are.
I told you before...
we come from the same place.
But I...
pray we don't end up the same.
Whatever, whoever says it to you.
I didn’t compromise.
I'm not a fucking criminal.
There's no end to this.
You try to run...
they hound you down.
They lose a head?
It grows right back.
If you want out...
you put them down.
All of them.
Eka, wait.
Why didn't you tell me you had
an undercover in there with Bangun?
What are you talking about?
Eka.
That piece of shit?
That piece of shit saved my life.
Yeah, he also cost the lives of ten
honest cops when he fed us bad intel.
He went rogue, Rama.
We lost him to Bangun.
And it never crossed your
mind to mention it to me?
Now's not the time for this.
The commissioner is dead.
Fucking bodies are piling
up all over the city.
I guess there's no such thing as
a clean war, lieutenant.
Maybe not.
But we still can get to Reza.
Luckily, we picked him up on Uco's wire.
What? They're together?
As far as we know.
We lost the signal,
but we're on our way.
I'm going to ask you one question.
And it's the only answer I want.
Is my family safe?
Yes, of course.
- Keep them that way.
- Wait, Rama, what… where…!
Watch over me.
Sir, would you like a tissue?
You better start walking if you
want your fucking tip.
I'm sorry, sir.
Of course we can. We can do
what we want, anything at all.
But there are…
always concessions to make.
New faces. New prices.
New prices?
Come on, Reza.
Just think of it as
a probation period.
How much did Goto pay you?
Now, that wouldn’t be
a smart question to ask.
Yeah, and why's that?
Because I'm meeting you. Not him.
Now think up a number.
If it keeps me here for
dessert, then it's enough.
Hey...
sidekick.
You're talkative.
Boss, boss…
he escaped from the car.
Put the word out.
Whoever finds him will be...
He's already here.
He's coming up.
- Then kill him.
- Yes, sir.
Everything okay?
Take care of it.
Reza...
don't worry.
Everything is… under control.
They’re more than capable of...
Motherfucker.
Gimme the ball.
"As usual."
No!
Reza!
No...
I'm done.